Behind the Line: Escape to Dunkirk is a war film directed by Ben Mole.
Occupied France, 1940.
A Nazi Commander discovers one of his prisoners, Danny is a champion boxer.
He forces him to fight for his company's entertainment.
But the POWs realise they can use these contests, as cover for an audacious breakout,
before they re sent to Germany, where escape will be almost impossible.
Their fate and freedom may all come down to how long Danny can keep fighting.
Danny Finnegan, played by Sam Gittins.
Maximus Sennenhund, played by Joe Egan.
Chantalle, played by Jennifer Martin.
Hauptsturmführer Drexler, played by Tim Berrington.
Tim Harper, played by Joel Phillimore.
Archie Bennett, played by Ryan Winsley.
Dunkirk is a 1958 British war film directed by Leslie Norman that depicts the Dunkirk evacuation
of World War II, and starring John Mills, Richard Attenborough, and Bernard Lee.
The film is based on the novels The Big Pick-Up by Elleston Trevor and
Dunkirk co-authored by Lt Col Ewan Butler and Major J.